{"flash_cards": [
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Hallo",
    "answer": "Здраво"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "sein",
    "answer": "Сум"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "haben",
    "answer": "Има"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "kaufen",
    "answer": "Купува"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "laufen",
    "answer": "трча"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "lesen",
    "answer": "чита"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "schreiben",
    "answer": "пишува"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "sollen",
    "answer": "треба"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "dürfen",
    "answer": "смее"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "wollen",
    "answer": "сака"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "Wasser",
    "answer": "вода"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "schlafen",
    "answer": "спи"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "Augen",
    "answer": "очи"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "Nase",
    "answer": "нос"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "Kopf",
    "answer": "глава"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "Geld",
    "answer": "пари"
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "Fuß",
    "answer": "стапало"
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "Gesicht",
    "answer": "лице"
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "Katze",
    "answer": "мачка"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "Hund",
    "answer": "куче"
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "Mädchen",
    "answer": "девојче"
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "Junge",
    "answer": "момче"
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "Mutter",
    "answer": "мајка"
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "Vater",
    "answer": "татко"
  }
]
}